[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "What do they need to say in order to justify and try to convince hesitant colleagues that this is the right thing to launch military strikes against targets in Syria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "Well, they're going to have a lot of questions.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "Based on all of our previous conversations, everything I've heard, Senator Corker, you're on board right now with the President, you're inclined to vote yea if the resolution were right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Well, I've said from day one as a result of what has happened that I would.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Corker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Is that the answer you've been getting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Wolf, I was in the region two and a half weeks ago and I was totally embarrassed and dismayed that not a single shipment of arms has yet made its way in the vetted opposition.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "What should the President do then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "You know, Wolf, I don't know what's going to happen in either body.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Why do you believe it's necessary now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Well, let's be clear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "What if he gets rejected there as David Cameron did in Britain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "EX", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Well, I feel confident that our colleagues, my colleagues both on the Republican side of the aisle as well as the Democratic side of the aisle are not going to jeopardize the credibility of the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Cameron"], "LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Why can't other countries do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Oh, there are other countries.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "NN", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Which countries will use their military power to attack targets inside Syria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Look, that's honestly something, Wolf I'm not of liberty to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Militarily?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "And that's going to be important.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Are you saying militarily?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Not just politically or vocally but militarily they will support the United States, they will go in with their F-16s, their own missiles, their firepower, and target sites in Syria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "In both military and diplomatic and political support, there are dozens of nations who had committed to back us up.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States", "Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Debbie Wasserman Schultz"]}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Congressman, why do you disagree so strongly with Debbie Wasserman Schultz's and with the President?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, of course I have great respect for my colleague, Debbie Wasserman Schultz, and she's been doing this a lot longer than I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Debbie Wasserman Schultz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "But do you believe that the intelligence that the Obama Administration has presented to you in classified briefings that it is 100 percent certain that the regime of Bashar al-Assad used sarin gas, poisoned gas to kill all those civilians?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "What language that I read in the classified documents and what I heard was highly confident.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Obama Administration"], "PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers Morgan"], "PERSON": ["Obama", "Wolf Blitzer"]}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NNPS", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "What message will we send if a dictator can gas hundreds of children to death in plain sight and pay no price?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "That was President Obama this week and I'm Wolf Blitzer and for Piers Morgan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "He will get the House of Representatives to authorize the use of military force?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Well, no, it is a political gamble.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House of Representatives"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Should the President have gone through this legislative route or should he have just done it without Congressional Law authorization?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Well, I command them for going this route because it think it portends for the future.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Are you afraid that even a limited strike could drag the United States into a prolonged conflict inside that Syrian civil war?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "I think the risk of that is relatively low.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Was he speaking carelessly or was he speaking thoughtfully?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "You know, we can't be sure of that but what we can be sure of is they don't seem to plot it out what would happen if that red line was crossed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Would it be catastrophic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Yes, I tend to think it would be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "If this is a really relatively modest Tomahawk cruise -- cruise missile strike for two or three days, will that accomplish much in the bigger picture of the civil war in Syria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", ":", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", ",", "MD", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "You know, I think that it actually had might.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Do you think -- you were just in Turkey, we saw your show yesterday, do you think the Turkish regime, the Turkish government would use military equipment, their NATO ally to bomb targets in Syria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I very much doubt it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NATO"], "LOCATION": ["Turkey", "Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Do you think it's possible?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "I think you can make him pay a price for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Do you want to make a final point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"], "LOCATION": ["Grenada", "Panama", "Libya"]}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Yes, you agree Doug Brinkley that this politically, historically speaking is a huge, huge moment in presidential history?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "It is, but that doesn't mean the next president's not going to have a Grenada, or Panama, or Libya, or some sort of intervention where they bypass Congress.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Doug Brinkley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Would executive authority be undermined down the road?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "No, I don't think so because it's all about the chemistry and the atmospherics of the moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Will he have the votes in the Senate and the House?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "HAPIRO: I think he will have the votes at the end of the day.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate", "House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130902pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "CD", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "It's going to be -- I mean you think it's going to just win by one or two votes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "One of two -- the number of people who will say to the leadership, \"I'm with you, if you absolutely need me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]